我应该把这个框起来
I oughta have this framed.
我最后的账单来自普林斯顿大学
My last bill from princeton.
我们要庆祝的是我终于毕业了
And I thought we were celebrating the fact,that I actually graduated.
我早就知道你肯定能毕业的
I always knew you'd be able to graduate.
我不知道的是我付不付的起这钱
What I didn't know was whether,I would be able to pay for it.
你妈妈
Your mom...
她以你为荣
she'd be so proud of you.
你总是这么说
You always say that.
我也以你为荣
I'm so proud of you.
一直都是
Always was.
哦,你要哭了
Come on, dad.You're gonna cry.
你不好意思了?
You wanna be embarrassed?
拥抱一下
You got it.
今晚别玩的太晚了
Look, um, don't party too hard tonight.
你奶奶要一张你捧着毕业证书的照片
Your grandmother wants a picture of you,getting that sheepskin.
你最好不要喝的醉醺醺的
And it'd be nice if you didn't look,completely hung over.
放心吧,不会的
no,don't worry.
我上个星期喝的酒都够我再上四年学了
I've had enough alcohol in the past week,to last meanother four years.
很好
Good...I think.
喝喝喝......
drink, drink, drink, drink,drink,
很好
drink, drink, drink!...
你真棒!
You are the man!
跟我讲讲技巧!
Tell me something I don't know!
这个不好玩,伙计
That's not funny, man.
什么?
What?
你电我
Yeah right. You shocked me.
用什么?我什么都没有
With what?I got nothing.
谁在用那个马上断开电源
All right, who ever's doing that,better cut it out!
怎么回事?
What the hell's going on?
可能是哪里短路了
maybe there's a short somewhere.
- 地上都是啤酒,- 不可能
-The floor's covered with beer.,-No way.
地板是防高压触电的,他的鞋也是橡胶绝缘的
The outlet's a gfi, plus he's got,rubber-soled shoes on.
快打911
somebody call 911!
House,第二季 第五集
House.,Season 2 Episode 5
病人有休克症状
Patient experiences shock-like sensations
还有头痛,恶心,睡意
as well as headaches, nausea, and drowsiness.
休克?
shocks?
极痛苦的休克
Excruciatingly painful shocks.
急症室医生把他交给了神经科
Er docs referred him to a neurologist,
在过去一周神经科又把他交给另外的5个医生
who referred him to five other doctors,in the last seven days.
休克可能是ihermitte's的表现
Shocks could be lhermitte's sign,
多样硬化症的早期症状
early symptom of ms.
不是,核磁共振显示没有脑脊髓白质损害
No, mri showed no white matter lesions,
休克没有伴随着头颈弯曲
and the shocks aren't accompanied,by neck flexing.
早上好
Good morning.
都中午了
It's almost noon.
真的?怪不得我这么饿
Really? That must be why I'm so hungry.
谁要去吃饭?
Who's up for lunch?
怎么穿夹克衫了?
What's with the jacket?
暖和,酷
It keeps me warm and cool.
谁知道
How does it know?
我们在说你的新病人
we're discussing your new patient.
哦,那肯定很枯燥
It must be a boring discussion
好像我还没接受一个新病人呢
seeing as I haven't accepted a new patient.
在我借你5000美元时你就接受了
You accepted him the moment I loaned,you five grand.
等等
wait, wait.
当我说我要为这钱做点事时
When I said I'd do anything for the money,
很明显我不是说我要收病人
obviously I didn't mean it.
你会喜欢这个的
You're gonna like this.
这个孩子每隔几分钟就休克一下
The kid's getting shocked every few minutes.
你为什么要5000美元
why would you need $5,000?
牌场失意还是情场得意?
Bad night at poker or a great night,with a hooker?
谢谢你为我解围
Thank you for saving me the trouble
不用开玩笑了
of deflecting that personal question,with a joke.
大学生?
College student?
有可能是派对上一氧化二氮搞的鬼
Nitrous oxide's fun at parties.
每天喝到吐为止
Can cause the shocks,
还能犯别的事
and drinking till you puke every night
给他一些b12.(维他命b12)
can cause everything else.
人在心不在
Give him some b12.
已经排除了癌症,多样硬化症,吡哆酶中毒,
Been there, done that.
以及所有的流行神经性疾病
and all the popular neuropathies.
颈脊椎病?
Cervical spondylosis?
不能解释这么低的白细胞
Doesn't explain the low white count.
他是黑人
He's black.
我假设他不只是黑而已
I'm assuming he's not just really dirty,
他应该有非洲家系
but is of african descent.
他白细胞这么低是什么意思?
Which means he'd have a lower white count.
没这么低
Not this low.
他是摔跤手
He's a wrestler.
也许他用利尿剂来减肥
Probably uses diuretics to cut weight.
这个也能引起低白细胞
It can also cause low white count.
不会这么低
Not this low.
贝西氏病
Behcet's.
没有皮肤损害
No skin lesions.
- 颈部疱疹损害了脊髓炎,- 没有外表损害
-Cervical herpes roster myelitis.,-No external outbreak.
有些东西不见了
Something's missing.
去找出来是什么
Find out what it is.
我还不知道是什么意思
I don't even know what that means.
去找出来
Well, figure it out, find it out,
然后来找我
and then find me.
我去吃饭了
I'll be at lunch.
毫无头绪?
No ideas?
太多了
Lots of ideas.
很多
Too many ideas.
所以才有这么多测试
That's why so many tests.
你吸过毒吗?
Have you used any recreational drugs?
什么?
What?
我会因为你吸毒了而生你的气?
I'm gonna get mad at you for getting stoned?
不是今天
Not today.
也不是这儿
Not here.
圣诞节时有个家伙过分兴奋了,我的意思的是,他
at christmas one of the guys had,some ecstasy, I mean, it was--
见鬼
Son of a bitch.
狼疮测试也是阴性的
Ana is negative for lupus...again.
豪斯要更多信息
House wants more information,
不是这些重复的再做一遍
not the same information done over again.
去把不见的找出来
Find what's missing.
我们所知道的就是他要死了
For all we know the kid is dying,
他在给我们猜谜?
and he's giving us riddles?
我找到更多的家庭病史
did a more detailed history,
祖宗三代
went back three generations.
- 还有?,- 他妈妈死于车祸
-And?,-His mom died in a car accident.
他外婆有关节炎
His mom's mom had arthritis,
他外曾祖父曾经在巴顿将军帅领的,黑人坦克团服役过
and his mom's mom's dad served inan all-black,tank battalion under patton.
好极了
Fascinating.
如果这不是肿瘤,那就是多样硬化症
If it's not a tumor, it has to be ms.
wilson已经否定这个了
Wilson already ruled out--
核磁共振不能100%的检测出多样硬化症
mri can't rule out ms 100% of the time.
多样硬化症不能解释为什么白细胞这么低
Ms doesn't explain a low white count.
酒精中毒可以解释
Alcoholism does.
他的细菌人工染色体检查为2.0
On admission his bac was 2.0.
肝化酶已经分解了它
Liver enzymes off the chart.
这是个毕业狂欢周末
It was graduation weekend.
他在这之前到几个星期里几乎都没喝酒
He barely drank in the weeks before that.
他在整个摔跤赛季根本就没喝酒
And he didn't drink at all during his,wrestling season.
如果你相信他的话
If you believe him.
我做了酒精测试
I did a tox screen--
她相不相信他不重要
it doesn't matter if she believes him or not.
但它确实有可能
It's already in the chart.
我们应该去找不见的东西
We're supposed to find out what's missing.
哇,这个
Well this--
太棒了
this is perfect.
星期三晚上请我去吃饭吧
Invite me to dinner thursday night.
我们还没有一起好好吃过饭呢
Come on. We haven't had a nice meal,together since
昨天我借你5000美元去买了辆新车
yesterday when I loaned you $5,000,to buy a new car.
我请客
My treat.
时速150英里的摩托车
Two-wheeled vehicles that travel 150 miles,an hour
这个瘸着腿又不负责的药罐子不配他
don't really go well with crippled,irresponsible drug addicts.
实际上摩托车每小时开180英里
Actually, two-wheeled vehicles that go,180 miles an hour
一个健康的,负责的设计师也不配他
do not go well with healthy,,responsible architects
不知道怎么区分刹车和转弯
who don't know how to separate,braking and turning.
好消息是降价了
The good news is it brings the price,right down.
你要把它退回去
You're taking it back.
妈呀
Mom.
讲讲我们要一起吃的饭吧
How 'bout we talk about this over dinner?
别提吃饭了
Forget dinner.
你要去自杀?
You're gonna kill yourself?
好车
nice bike.
谢了
Thank you.
看吧,这才是你该做的
See, that's how you do it.
恭维,晚饭
Compliments, dinner.
你的拐杖怎么办?,请我吃饭我就告诉你
What do you with your cane?
Evel knievel(魔幻摩托车游戏)有一样的构造
Evel knievel had the same set up.
他摔断了他全身的骨头
And he broke every bonein his body.
我们研究了所有的影像
we went through all the imaging studies
重做了血细胞培养
and redid the blood culturesand...
我不要那些旧东西,我要新信息
I don't want hand-me-downs.,I want brand new stuff.
什么都没有
There's nothing--
什么都没有不见
there's nothing missing!
对不起我没有听到最后一点
Sorry, I didn't catchthat last part.
我们什么都不能做
There's nothing elsewe can do.
你们查了警局记录没有?
You check the police report?
查什么?
On what?
她妈妈的车祸
On his mom's car accident.
那个发生在15年前了
It was 15 years ago.
那孩子根本就不在车上
The kid wasn't even in the car.
她突然驶离了直线,在大白天干燥的宽马路上
She veered off a straight,,dry road in broad daylight.
你对这点不奇怪吗?
That doesn't seem odd to you?
可能她正在换电台或做其它的事而分心了
She probably got distracted changing radio,stationsor something.
警察也这么想的
That's whatthe police thought.
他们当然不知道她是这个家的一员
Of course they didn't know that she has,a family member
经常性的休克,还可以做事?
who is frequently incapacitated by,shock-like sensations.
基因分析排除这种可能性
A genetic componentseems unlikely.
这很有意思
But it's interesting.
一种纤维神经瘤症可能会引起这种休克
A type two neurofibromatosiscould,cause the shock.
你早就知道这个被漏掉了?
You knew this was missing?
我只知道某样东西被漏掉了
I knew something was missing.
也许是这个,也许是别的
Maybe this.Maybe something else.
对第22对长染色体做DNA分析
Get a dna analysis of the long arm ,of chromosome 22.
你真的要跟你妻子吃饭?
You'd rather have dinnerwith your wife?
是的,我会的...,如果她跟我说话的话
Yes, I would...if she were speaking to me.
跟她不一样,
Unlike her,
我值得你跟我一起吃饭
I could make it worth your while.
好
Fine.
我要开车吗
Should I drive?
不
no.
直到我看见你的钱包我才让你上我的车
And I'm not letting you in mycar until,I see your wallet.
nf2是一种遗传病
Nf2, it'san inherited disease.
这会引起头盖骨神经的不正常生长
It could cause abnormal growths on,the cranial nerves.
这可以解释这种症况下的休克
It would explain the shocksand other symptoms.
DNA分析可以显示你的儿子,是否有哪种具体的染色体变异
Dna analysis will show whether your son,has the specific chromosome mutation
引起了这种病
which causes the disease.
但是如果它是遗传的
But if it's inherited
这就使说我们家其他人有这个病
that means someone else in our family would, have it.
我们认为你妻子可能有这个病
We think your wifemay have had it.
不,她身体一向很健康
No, she never had anysort of health problems.
没有难看的雀斑?虹膜里没有小块?
No odd-looking freckles?Nodules in the iris?
没有
nothing.
为什么你们认为她有病
Why would you thinkshe was sick?
我们认为她的车祸另有原因
We think it may have beenwhat caused,her car accident.
等一下,这是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean?
我妈妈的车被一个醉鬼撞了
My mom's car was hitby a drunk driver.
警察的调查报告里可不是这么写的
That's not whatthe police report indicated.
你们看到的肯定是错的报告
You must have gottenthe wrong report.
不
No.
他们没错
They didn'T.
当你开始开车时,我,
When you started driving,I,
你撒谎了?
you lied about how mom died?
我觉得她至少可以不用白白死掉
I figured if her death could somehow,mean something--
不用白白死掉是什么意思?
how's lying about itmean something?
你怎么这么利用她,爸爸?
How could you use her like that, dad?
她的死?
Her death?
我只是想保护你
I was just tryingto protect you.
还有什么是假的
What else isn't true?
她不是个老师?
She wasn't a teacher.
你只想我读书？
You just wanted me to read?
这是什么味道
What's that smell?
我没闻到
I don't smell...
我们要叫个护士
we're gonna need a nurse.
天
What the hell?
没问题，我们会搞定的
It's okay.We'll take care of it.
你没感觉到？
You didn't feel anything?
没有
No.
痛吗？
You feel that?
但是你不知道你要方便?
But you didn't feel any of this?
没有
No.
肛门括约肌麻痹症加上休克等于米勒费雪综合症
Sphincter paralysis plus shocksequals miller,fisher syndrome.
如果你加上他的大便样品,显示的是空肠弯曲菌阴性,就不算米勒费雪综合征了
Not if you add the stool sample,which is negative,for C.Jejuni.
他在她妻子的死上对他儿子撒谎了?
He lied to his son about how his mom died?
他只想保护他
he was just protecting him.
操纵他
Manipulating him.
父母都这么做
That's what parents do.
他们对我们撒谎是因为他们爱我们
They lie to us because they love us.
谁想要哭?
Who's getting teary?
母亲的死没有关系
Mom's death is irrelevant.
DNA分析显示没有神经纤维肿瘤迹象,或别的遗传疾病
Dna revealed no nf2 markersor any other,inherited disease.
很显然,她在开车时的确睡着了
Apparently, she really did fall asleep,at the wheel.
我们现在到底在讨论什么?
So what exactlyare we talking about here?
一点偷窥就让草原犬鼠
A little peekeror did the prairie dog
从洞里出来玩?
actually come out to play?
对不起?
Excuse me?
我们在讲爆炸吗?
Are we talking explosive?
潜血检查呈阴性
The hemacultwas negative for blood.
我不会讲他真的爆炸了
And I wouldn't say he actually exploded.
更像大量涌出
More like gushed.
我们有一些进展了
Good.We're getting somewhere.
真的?什么地步?
Yeah?Where?
我不知道
I have no idea.
当然,我们爱猜谜语
Of course.Love the riddles.
嗨,妈妈
hi, mom.
呃,我星期三晚上有个饭局
Look, I have a business dinneron,thursday night.
我推不掉
I can't get out of.
我知道,我也很想见你们
I know.I really wanted to see you too.
我过会儿给你回电话,现在在开会
Actually, can I call you back?,I'm in a meetingright now.
好,谢谢
Okay, thanks.
谁打的?
Who was that?
安吉利娜 卓琳.我妈妈
Angelina jolie.I call her mom.
谁觉得这个好笑?
Who thinks that's sexy?
到底是爆炸还是大量涌出?
So explosive or gushing?
她从来不打这里的电话.有事吗?
She never calls here.Is everything okay?
没事,很好
Great.Yeah.
我爸爸要带她去欧洲
My dad's taking her to europe.
他们周三要在纽约停留9小时
They got a nine-hour layoverin newark,on thursday.
如果这时肠胃的-
If it's gastrointestinal--
你为了不见你妈妈而撒谎?
you lied to avoid seeingyour own mom?
你在开玩笑?我从来不对妈妈说谎.
Are you kidding?I can't lie to my mom.
很认真的,我不能
Seriously, I can'T.
Wilson 请我吃饭
Wilson's invited me to dinner.
放一个借了我5000大洋的人鸽子,不是明智之举
It would be rudeto stand up a guy who just,loaned me five grand.
横向脊髓炎?
Transverse myelitis?
这个能使他失去知觉,肛门括约肌失去功能
It causes numbness, anal sphincter dysfunction.
还有休克
And the shocks.
多谢你转移话题了
Thank you for taking no interestin my mother.
现在避开这个问题,什么引起了横向脊髓炎?
That begs the question, whatcaused,the transverse myelitis?
我们排除了癌症和多样硬化症.就剩感染了.
We've ruled out cancer and ms.Leaves infection.
如果有感染,那就有发热
If there was infection,there'd be a fever.
他的血液和脑脊液分析都是阴性的
And his blood and csf culturesare already,negative.
也许感染已经好了,但是记忆还停留在那
Maybe the infection's gone,but the memory remains.
分子模拟,好极了
Molecular mimicry.Nice.
现在去拿一台免疫球蛋白分析仪和电泳仪
Now get an immunoglobulin leveland,electrophoresis.
你很棒.我相信我们会再见面的
You're good, my friend.I'm sure we'll meet again.
你真的认为那是他妈妈打的电话?
You really thinkthat was his mom on the phone?
也许吧,我只是搞不懂他为什么要撒这个谎.
Probably, I don't know whyhe'd lie about that.
管他呢
Who cares?
你一点都不好奇他父母什么样的?
You're not the least bit curious,what his parents are like?
我肯定他的她妈妈的一件作品
I'm sure his mom'sa piece of work.
只有妈妈才能做出这么大的毁害
Only a mother could dothat much damage.
我敢打赌他生下来就是这样的
My bet's he was born the way he is.
刚好相反,也许是他折磨他的父母呢?
Probably tormented his parents,not the, other way around.
他既跑不快也不会打架
He was either a fast runneror one hell, of a fighter.
你去哪里?
Where you going?
你们能搞定这些测试的,对吧?
You guys can handlethe tests, right?
你和豪斯有很重要的事非要在吃饭时讨论?
Is there something important that
放高利贷
Other thanthe skyrocketing interest rates,on personal loans?
你知道,这是第四次
You know,this is the fourth time
我借他钱了.不是吃饭的钱--钱
I've loaned him money.Not lunch money--money, ,money.
豪斯的父母？
House's parents?
周三晚上他们要在纽约逗留
They have a layover in newark thursday evening.
我取消这顿饭
I'm canceling dinner.
不用,其实我觉得你可以邀请更多的人
No, I thought maybe you couldjust invite,a few more people.
传染性的药剂的分子结构跟脊柱分子的很像
an infectious agent'smolecular structure can,resemble the spinal cord'S.
当免疫系统攻击感染时
When the immune systemattacks the infection
它也会停止攻击脊柱细胞
it ends up attackingthe spinal cord's as well.
这么说他被感染了
So he hasan infection.
他们刚说我没感染
They just said I don'T.
即便没有感染了,它还是会继续攻击
Even after the infection isgone,,it goes right on attacking
因为脊柱束仍然在
because the spinal cordis still there.
有治疗方法吗?
is there a treatment?
这得看感染源是什么
Depends on whatthe original infection was.
很好,你做到了
All right, you're done.
你要平板上躺一个小时做腰神经刺穿
You need to lay flat after a lumbar puncturefor,about an hour.
我要吐了
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
爸爸,给我拿罐可乐吧
Hey dad, can you get mea coke please?
好,他们通常很有用
Yeah, that usually helps.
你吐了
You're done.
如果你觉得恶心
If you're nauseous--
不,我不恶心
no, I'm not nauseous.
我只想他离开这
I just want him outta here.
他是你爸爸
He's your dad.
他会一直在你身边
He's gonna be around.
是的,我知道
Yeah, I know.
不是这个,那是....
it's not that, it'S...
难道就没有人讲真话了吗?
are these peoplecompletely incapable
他跟朋友去过牙买加
of telling the truthto each other?
怪不得他撒谎了
No wonder he lied.
家长认为孩子们不应该到处玩
Children aren't supposedto have good times.
他的一个朋友带他们去的
One of his friendsflew them down.
Carnel的爸爸不能接受他的有钱朋友
Carnell's dad has this thing about him accepting,stuff from rich friends.
他希望他儿子不要忘本
Wants him to remember who he is, and where, he came from.
你去哪里了?
Where have you been?
订餐了.什么事?
Making dinner plans.What's up?
这孩子说出了惊人的事实
The boys have uncoveredthe shocking fact
他跟父亲关系不好
that the patient has a crappy relationship,with his dad.
他们看上去很在乎对方
They seem to actually care.
哦,我不这么认为
well, I don'T.
任何一个孩子去牙买加都只有一个原因
There's only one reason any kidwith a plane,flies to jamaica.
不是因为大麻
It wasn't for marijuana.
他什么都没做只是喝酒
He doesn't do anythingbut drink.
他这么跟你说还是这么跟他爸爸说?
He said that to youor his pops?
四氢大麻醇检测显示阴性
Tox screen was negative for thc.
春假一个月前结束了
Spring break wasover a month ago.
就算酒瓶子都被冲掉了
Even pot would havewashed out by now.
就算他吸大麻了
Even if he'd smoked,
也不可能会引起横向脊髓炎啊?
no way marijuanacauses transverse myelitis?
对,但是他们放的这个东西可以引起
True, but the stuffthat they put on it does.
农药
Pesticides.
为什么他对旅行说了实话
Why would he come cleanabout the trip,
而在吸大麻上撒谎?
but lie about smoking pot?
他也不可能因为吸毒而得了农药中毒啊
He wouldn't have necessarily have to smoke,to get pesticide poisoning.
他可能吃了撒了农药的水果
He could have eaten fruitthat had been sprayed
或者在徒步时暴露出他的皮肤
or been exposedthrough his skin on a hike.
或者他吸了这个
Or he could have smoked it.
反正很多原因.撒谎了
A lot of it.And lied about it.
这是因为他家就是这么做的
Because that's whatthis family does.
给他注射氯解磷定剂
Start him on iv pralidoxime.
每升两克
Two grams per liter,
每8小时注射一克直到你看到成效
then one gram every eight hours until,you see improvement.
你没有证据支持中毒诊断
You have no evidence to supporta poisoning, diagnosis.
什么是为什么这会变得很酷
Which is whyit's gonna be so cool
当我证明我是对的时候
when I turn out to be right.
cameron.
cameron
你跟谁一起吃晚饭
Who are you makingdinner plans with?
没人
No one.
你说谎
you bastard.
你邀请我父母吃晚饭
You invited my parents to dinner.
天哪,cameron是个大嘴巴
Jeez, cameron's gota big mouth.
没你的大
not as big as yours.
喂,你为了不见你父母而利用我
Hey, you used meto avoid seeing your parents.
你想怎么样?
What do you care?
我不想怎么样.我只想知道为什么
I don't, I just thought it might be interesting,to find out why.
你就不能问我么？
You could have just asked.
你撒谎了
You would have lied.
你应该相信我
And you would have believed me,
怎样才能让我们都满意呢
which would have keptus both happy.
你想拿回你的钱?就是这个?
You want your money back?,Is that what this is about?
不
No!
等等,好,你手头有钱了吗?
Wait--well--have you got the money?
如果你拿到钱了,你为什么还要借?
If you have the money, then why did you ,need the loan?
我没有
I didn'T.
我只想看看你是不是肯给我
I just wanted to see if you'd give it to me.
自从你去年借了我40美元后,我就越借越多
I've been borrowing increasing amounts,ever since you lent me $40 a year ago.
一个小实验可以看出你的底线在哪里
A little experiment to see whereyou draw the line.
你在测量我们友谊的价值?
You're--you're trying toobjectively measure,how much I value our friendship?
5000美金
It's five grand.
你不会觉得这样可耻的
You got nothingto be ashamed of.
那你怎么说
So what do you say?
一个电话交换支票
One little phone call,one big check.
好
Fine.
谢谢
Thanks.
现在你长大了,就可以告诉你爸妈你不想再见到他们了
Now be a grownupand either tell mommy and daddy,you don't want to see them,
或者我带你去吃晚饭,7点
or I'm picking you up at 7:00 for dinner.
什么意思
What do you mean?
- 你刚才说,- 我撒谎了
-You just said that,- --I lied.
自从一年前我跟你说你不刮胡须会比较好看
I've been lying to youin increasing amounts
我对你讲的实话就越来越少了
ever since I told you you looked good,unshaved a year ago.
这只是个小实验,你知道的
It's a little experiment,you know,
看看你的底线
see where you draw the line.
病人怎么样?
how's the patient?
今天还没进展
haven't been in yet today.
只要他不恶化
As long as he hasn'tgotten any worse.
你在没有任何中毒的证明下就让他按中毒治疗
You're treating himfor pesticide poisoning,without any proofof pesticides.
我们没有办法跟我们的律师这么解释
We're gonna have a hellof a time explaining that,to our lawyer.
我叫豪斯别这么做了
I told house not to...
律师不会相信这套的
Lawyer's not gonna believe this.
他的胃口又回来了
He's got his appetite back.
不管你做了什么,它起作用了
Whatever you did,it's working.
他康复了,所有的都可以原谅了
He's healthy,so all is forgiven.
现在我觉得恶心
Now I'm feelingnauseous.
他没有康复
He is not healthy.
恶心和腹泻不是他唯一的症状
Nausea and diarrheawere not his only symptoms.
休克也减少了
Shocks havealso decreased.
但是没有消失
But not disappeared.
他不用包尿布了
And he's outof the diaper,
这对每个人来说都是好消息
which is good newsfor everyone.
那他的低白细胞怎么解释
What about his low white count?
这些小球需要时间来增长
The little buggersneed time to grow.
别担心,我们的摔跤手信仰的拉斯特教也会回来的
Don't worry, our wrestlingrastafarian,will be back on his feet
马上就会在爸爸的后背躲起来
and sneaking around behindpop's back again ,in no time.
再检查一遍
Check it again.
我马上过去
I'll be right there.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我把带菌者转到遥远的外地去,就可以省一大笔钱了
Apparently I can save moneyby switching to,anotherlong-distance carrier.
我对的,不是吗?
I was right.Wasn't I?
是啊,你永远都是对的
Oh yeah, it's alwaysabout you, isn't it?
他在颤抖,体温在上升
He has the chills andhis temperature is spiking.
到106度了
It's nearly 106.
什么意思
what's that mean?
我问发生什么事了?
I mean, what's happened?
你想知道真相?
do you want the truth?
你要我编故事来让你安心吗?
Do you want me to make somethingup to protect you?
一个醉鬼开车冲进了他的房间
We think a drunk driverbroke into his room.
我儿子怎么了?
What's happeningto my son?
真相是我不知道
The truth is I have no idea.
cameron正在找发烧的原因
There's the feverthat cameron was looking for.
如果是脊髓炎的话这里应该有"itis"
We knew if was myelitisthere had to be an "itis."
肯定是感染引起的
This must be the infectionthat set it off.
除非这个病例太与众不同
Yeah, except in this universeeffect follows cause.
我对这个很不满,但是
I've complained about it, but--
也许检测都错了
maybe the tests were wrong.
不,检测是对的
no, the tests were right.
昨天他没有发热也没有感染
Yesterday he had no fever.No infection.
那就是他在这里时受到细菌感染了?
So he just happened to catcha bug,while he was here?
就是这个?
That's all this is?
因为他的白血细胞数正在下降
Yeah, because his white bloodcell count was down,
他现在失去免疫力了
he was vulnerable.
因为白细胞数很低,很可能会杀死他
Because it's really down, it might kill him,
就是这个
but that's all this is.
他还是大小便失禁?
Is he still pooping his pants?
他又开始了
He just started again.
又?
Again?
当他有点好转时停过
It stopped when hewas getting better.
他只是感到好多了,他从没真正好多了
He was feeling better.,He was never getting better.
那么我们所要回答的就是,到底是什么使一个22岁的孩子
So all we haveto answer is what causesa ,22-year-old kid
变成免疫系统崩溃,胰岛素混乱,还有休克?
to becomeimmuno-compromised with gi involvement,and shocks?
那些结束开始都没有明显的原因
That stop and startfor no apparent reason.
在他被感染杀死前我们要找出答案
We need to find an answerbefore this infection ,kills him.
这样最理想了
Yeah, that'd be the ideal.
你给他注射静脉抗生素
You, intravenousbroad spectrum antibiotics.
再去做个核磁共振
You get a cervical thoracicand lumbar t2,weighted fast spin echo mris.
还有你,去找出来都有谁一起去了牙买加
And you, track down all those richie riches,who went to jamaica.
看看都有谁休克,腹泻或发热
See if any of them got theshocks, the trots,, or the hots.
就是发烧
The hots, it's fever.
要不要周三跟我们一起吃饭?
You guys gonna join usfor dinner thursday?
我要洗衣服
gotta do my laundry.
你们不好奇?
You're not curious?
我对鳄鱼很好奇,不过我不想把头放到它嘴里面
Curious about crocs,but I don't stick,my headin their mouths.
我也不去.豪斯是个变态
I'm out too.House is a freak.
没有病毒引起这个,也没有染色体变异
There's no virus thatcauses that, no dna mutation.
你要和两个人吃一顿饭
You're gonna haveone dinner with two people.
一个小时,大部分时间都在咀嚼
60 minutes,most of it spent chewing,
讲些天气
talking about the weather.
除了一些他们感兴趣的话题
Unless they something like,
"哪种葡萄酒你更喜欢,chardonnayor还是merlot"
"do you prefer the chardonnayor the merlot
我们把greg锁在阁楼里17年
--we kept greg lockedin the closet for 17 years
你还是什么都不知道
"you're not gonna learn anything.
好
Okay.
我们想跟你一些朋友谈谈
we'd like to talk to some of your friends,
看看他们是不是也有一样的症状
see if they haveany similar symptoms.
急症室的医生已经问过我这些了
the doctors in the er already asked me that.
我们理解
we understand.
但他们没有我们现在有的信息
But they didn't have allthe information ,we have now.
什么样的信息
What kind of information?
我能跟carnell单独讲几句吗?
Would you mind if I spoke with carnell,alone for a minute?
这是坏消息?
Is this bad news?
不.只是些私密问题
No.It's just confidential.
为什么突然变成私密问题了?
Why is somethingsuddenly confidential?
我的意思是如果你知道我儿子一些事
I mean, if you know something about my son,
我要知道发生什么事情了
I need to know what's going on.
对不起我要坚持
I'm sorry.I have to insist.
我是他爸爸
I'm his father.
如果我要去照顾他
And if I'm goingto take care of him,
我需要知道真相
I need to know the truth.
爸爸,她想知道我跟谁去了牙买加
Dad, she wants to knowwho I went to jamaica with.
你从来没去过牙买加
You never been to jamaica.
taddy的爸爸在春假时带我们去了那里
Taddy's dad flew a bunchof us down ,over spring break.
你跟我说春假要写两篇论文
You told me you had two papersto write, over the break.
因为我不想回家干活干的累死
'Cause I didn't wanna come homeand work, my ass off.
我只想好好的放一次真正的假
I wanted to take an actual breakduring the break, for once.
我不应该骗你
I shouldn't have lied to you.
不,你应该做的事是回家
No, what you shoulda doneis come home
而不是跟你的有钱朋友出去玩
instead of partying with your rich friends.
对不起,我们需要那些人的名字
I'm sorry.We need those names.
你想要什么
What do you want?
道歉
To apologize.
我发现我对门诊部的关心有些太迟了
I realize that my attention to the clinichas,been somewhat lax of late,
我觉得要改变一下
and I want to make amends.
明天晚上怎么样?
How 'bout tomorrow night?
我值晚班
I take the night shift.
门诊部9点关门
The clinic'sclosed at night.
是的,不过我相信会有很多事情要做
Yeah, but I'm sure there'splenty of things, to be done.
一些表格要检查,补给,排列
There's charts to be reviewed,supplies, inventoried--
只要不吃饭
dinners avoided.
你也要去?
You're going too?
我爱死他们的色拉了
I love theircobb salad.
给我个理由
Give me a reasonto get out of this,
我就告诉你谁造的谣说你做过变性手术
and I'll tell youwho started the rumor,about youbeing a transsexual.
没有这种谣言
There is no such rumor.
如果你不帮我推掉晚饭就会有这种谣言了
There will be unless you get meout of this dinner.
没有人逼你这么做,豪斯
No one's makingyou do this, house.
就像每一个人做的那样,对他们撒谎
Just do what everybody elsedoes, lie to them.
你对你妈妈撒谎了?
You lie to your mother?
12岁时
Only since I was 12.
我妈妈是人类学作家
My mom's a human polygraph.
我爸爸应该带她去拉斯维加斯而不是卢浮宫
My dad should be taking herto vegas, ,not the louvre.
相信我,你妈妈绝对相信你是在开会
Trust me, your momwould much rather think
而不是讨厌她
you have a business meetingthan you hate her.
我不讨厌她
I don't hate her.
我讨厌他
I hate him.
我们都头痛,恶心,呕吐
we all had headaches,nausea, vomiting.
我们认为这跟酗酒有关
We figured it was connected to the massive,amountsof drinking.
你觉得Carnell的病跟的旅行有关?
You think what happenedto carnell has something,to dowith the trip?
不知道
Don't know.
在你回来后没有任何没法解释的疼痛,或奇怪的感觉吗?
You haven't had any unexplained pain or,strangefeelings since you got back?
是,除了一些运动痛外,我很好
Nope, except for a littleathlete's foot, I'm fine.
我能看看吗?
Can I see it?
看什么?
See what?
你的脚
Your feeT.
在牙买加有种寄生虫会在脚部聚积，使脚肿大
There's a common parasitein jamaica that,can resemble foot fungus.
我的脚没有
It's not really my feet.
我是说肿大
You know, I figuredfungus is fungus.
这是我的鼠蹊
It's my groin.
我要看看它
I'm going to needto take a look at that.
现在?
Now?
那你想跟我一起下到医院?
Unless you wanna come downto the hospital with me.
不是,我不能,我两天前才开始
No, I can't, I mean,I just started two days ago,
- 我们就在办公室中间,- 脱裤子
-and we're rightin the middle of a big merg--,-then drop your pants.
呃,我需要-
Reilly, I need the--
怎么回事?
what the hell's going on here?
她是医生
She's a doctor.
我是医生,他出疹了
I'm a doctor.He has a rash.
- 也是他的朋友,- 对
-And a friend of his,- --right.
好,等她治好你的皮疹
Well, as soon as she'sdone treating your rash,
我需要d-port技术的号码
I need the numbers on d-port technology.
好的
Yes, sir.
医生,走时留个名片吧
And doctor, why don't you leave a card,on your way out?
不算一个出疹的男人
except for one guy with a rash
旅行中没有人有生病
no one else on the triphas any health issues.
哪种皮疹?
What kind of rash?
我不知道.我检查了一些
I don't know.I took some scrapings.
不像是癣
It doesn't appearto be ringworm.
看上去像什么
What did it look like?
不是癣是什么?
Aside from not ringworm.
像是衣物过敏
Basically like diaper rash.
他一直工作没停过
He's been working around the clock.
他三天没换衣服了
Said he hasn't changedhis clothes in three days.
卡波西式肉瘤看上去像衣物过敏
Kaposi's sarcoma canlook like diaper rash.
周围有没有变色?
Any discolorationaround the edges?
带他过来,我要看看
Get him in here.We all wanna take a look.
就算这是卡波西式肉瘤,也没有什么关系
Even if it is kaposi's, it's not related.
病人没有任何皮肤上的症状
The patient doesn't haveany skin symptoms.
而且我们已经排除了癌症了
And we've alreadyruled out cancer.
这种可能性会有多大
What are the odds of two friends
两个朋友刚刚一起从外国回来
who've just returned from a trip outside,the country coming down
都有无法解释的病,却没有一点联系?
with unexplained,but unrelated illnesses?
带他过来,他不会过来
Get him in here. He won't come.
毕业后他才找到一份新工作
Just started a new jobafter graduation.
他们在一个大公司里工作
They're workingon some big merger.
跟他说他的朋友命悬一线了
Tell him his friend's life hangsin the balance.
我一开始也是这么说的
That's what I told him the first time.
还是不会来曼哈顿的
Still wound up drivinginto manhattan.
告诉他他要没命了
Tell him his life hangsin the balance.
告诉他他的皮疹会吃肉
Tell him the rash is flesh-eating,
下一步在菜单上就是他了
and the next course on the menu is,his frank and beans.
stacy在哪里?
Where is stacy?
在巴尔的摩主持会议
speaking at a conferencein baltimore.
干什么?你要什么?
Why?What do you need?
我能给一个病人发传票吗?
Can I subpoena a patient?
豪斯要我把那个孩子给骗过来
House wants me to lie to the kidto get him, in here.
好,那你就有传票了
Well, then you'll be the onegetting the subpoena.
我们真的需要诊断他的朋友
Well, we do need himto diagnose his friend.
给这孩子做这个检测
Take the testto the kid.
没有检测,豪斯只想看一下
There is no test.House just wants to look at it.
那就叫豪斯做这个测试
Then take houseto it.
就像这就要发生了
Yeah, like that'sgonna happen.
告诉豪斯他父母打过电话来了
Tell house his parents called.
说他们会早点来
Said they were coming in early.
他为了逃避他们哪里都会去的
He'll go anywherejust to avoid them.
那就可以对豪斯撒谎而不能对病人撒谎?
So it's okay to lie to house,but not,to a patient?
怎么了?
what's wrong?
他的胃越来越差了
His stomach's gettinga lot worse.
他变僵硬了
He's rigid.
他腹部出血
He's bleedinginto his abdomen.
然后呢?
what's going on?
我们要动手术
We need a surgeonand an O.R., Stat.
感染引起了他的s形孔结肠
Infection caused a perforationin his ,sigmoid colon.
这个可以修复的
It's repairable.
这说明抗生素没有用
It means the antibioticsaren't working.
加倍剂量
double the dose.
加进甘氨酰四环素类(tygacil)
And add tygacil to the list.
就等他出手术室
As soon as he'sout of surgery.
richeie在哪里?
Where's richie rich?
他说他不能离开工作
He said he can't leave work.
你两小时前就这么跟我说了
you told me thattwo hours ago.
我没有打算撒谎
I'm not gonna lie.
为什么,因为撒谎是不对的?
Why?Because it's wrong?
还是因为你是懦夫?
Or because you'rea coward?
艰难的选择
tough choice.
你在浪费这孩子两个小时的时间
You'd be wasting two hoursof the kid's time.
这是无法原谅的深刻的道德错误吗?
Is that deeplyand unforgivably morally wrong?
不是
No.
因为这不是在浪费他的时间
Because it's nota waste of his time.
除非我们都错了
Unless we're wrong.
除非他的状况和他的朋友无关
Unless his condition's gotnothing to do,with his friend'S.
你只是害怕犯错
You're just afraidof being wrong.
你父母打过电话来了
Your parents called.
你们要搭早--
They had to catch an earlier--
你不需要跟他撒谎
you don't have to lie to him.
他在路上了
Kid's on his way here.
他下班了?
He got off work?
吐血
by vomiting blood.
救护车10分钟前开出了
Ambulance is ten minutes out.
- 你是taddy?,- 是的
-You taddy?,-What?
我爱这个名字.我从没来没有一只狗...
I love the name.I never had a dog...
脱他的裤子
take off his pants.
不要跟她讲话.听我说
Don't talk to her.Listen to me.
他吐了超过三单位的血
he's vomited in excess of three units of blood.
他需要住院-
He needs to be admitted bef--
如果你想做一名医生
if you wanted to be a doctor,
也许你在高中时可以再加把劲
maybe you should have buckled down a little,more in high school.
咬我
Bite me.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
你和carnell到底有多近?
Exactly how closewere you and carnell?
没有这么近
Not so close.
在牙买加大部分时间都在一起?
Spend a lot of time togetherin jamaica?
睡一间房?
Share a room?
等一下,你不是认为
Wait, you don't think--
喂,我们不是同性恋
look, we're not gay.
我没说你是同性恋
I'm not saying you're gay.
我是说你有过性生活
I'm saying you had sex.
我们不是同性恋,我们基本不出去
Look, we're not gay.We hardly even hung out.
好,那你带他去牙买加因为他赢了比赛
Right, you flew himdown to jamaica,because he won a contest.
不是,他是我们联谊会成员
No, he's in my frat.
在上课和摔跤期间一有空就回家
Between school and wrestlingand going home ,every break
在他爸的废物堆积场干活
to work at hisfather's junkyard,
carnell根本就没有时间跟人出去
carnell didn't have any timeto hang out ,with anybody.
这不是菌状肿
it's not fungus.
我早就告诉你了
I already told you that.
没有脓包.这不是葡萄状球菌
There's no pustules.It's not staph.
他爸爸的什么?
His dad's what?
他爸爸有个废金属回收场
His dad ownsa scrap metal salvage yard.
Carnell在放假时在那干活
Carnell worked thereduring breaks.
你撒谎
You lied.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
当然,在这样的家庭里你需要更多细节
of course,in this family you probably needmore, specifics.
你跟我说你有个建筑公司,不是废物回收场
You told us you owneda construction company,,not a salvage yard.
我知道是怎么回事
I knowthe way things work.
我的工作越好,我儿子受到的治疗就会越好
The better my job,the better my son gets treated.
对,这就是我为什么要生气
Right, that's why I'm mad.
我们白白浪费了这么多时间
We wasted all thatfilet mignon on you.
在你儿子最后一次为你干活时发现什么异常的没有?
Did your kid findanything unusual the last,timehe worked for you?
- 没有,- 编织线?
-No.,-Braided wire?
两头是金属的铅罐
Metal weights on each end,a lead canister,
也许就是个盖子
maybe just the lid.
也许他拿来做门挡或压纸器
He probably used it asa doorstop or a paperweight.
他为什么要用
Why would he wanna--
好
okay, here it comes.
我给他的早期的毕业礼物是个我找到的铅锤
I gave him an early graduationgift, ,an old plumb I found.
就像鱼秤
It looks like a fishing weight.
我把它放在钥匙链上
I put iton a keychain,
这样他就可以不会忘本了
so he'd always rememberwhere he came from.
这样他以后就可以靠这个了
So he can lieabout it later.
钥匙链在哪里?
Where's the keychain?
我不知道
I don't know.
他从来不用
He never used it.
只把它当作一个护身符
Just kept itas a good luck charm.
放在哪里了?
Kept it where?
我不知道
I don't know.
为什么?
Why?
这个有关系吗?
Why does it matter?
他的衣服在哪里?
Where are the kid's clothes?
在他的房间的衣柜后
In the bureauback in his regular room.
你们两个把它拿去检查放射线
You two, get itto radiology.
他的衣服?
His clothes?
衣柜
The bureau.
别打开
Don't open it.
你跟我来
You, come with me.
放在这
set it down there.
然后离开这.它有放射性
Now get out of here.This thing is radioactive.
可能的辐射导致中枢神经系统症状
The chances of radiationcausing cns symptoms...
可以把那个孩子叫做穿着含铅睡衣的人
Call the boysin the lead pajamas.
浓度还没有高到引起中枢神经系统损伤
Emweren't high enough to causecentral nervous,system damage.
它也许还没有引起中枢神经损伤
It might not have causednerve damage,
但毫无疑问它破坏了免疫系统
but it definitely destroyed his immune system.
还有引起肿瘤
And caused tumors.
我们还不知道
we don't know that.
核磁共振没有显示任何证据
None of the mrisshowed anything.
做正电子放射断层扫描
Do a pet scan.
检查他的中枢脊椎
Check his cervical spine.
看上去不太妙
It's not gonna begood news.
对不起,坏消息
I'm sorry, it's not good news.
你给carnell的那片金属
The piece of metal that you gave carnell
在工业上是用来探测矿井的
was from an industrial device used to test wells.
人们不应该乱丢放射性材料
People aren't supposed to justdump radioactive,material.
但他们扔了
But they do.
那现在怎么办?
So what now?I mean, what do you do?
任何人跟这个金属有过接触的
anyone who has had contact with the source
要马上接受放射系疾病的治疗
will have to immediately get treatment,for radiation sickness.
Taddy开车时把它放在腿上
Taddy carried iton his lap on a drive.
有治疗办法吗?
So there is a treatment?
静脉注射
Transfusions.
我们会试着平衡电解质
And we try to get the fluidsand the electrolytes, balanced.
Carnel--他被辐射的更多
Carnell--he's hadmuch more exposure.
相当于70,000次x光胸透
The equivalentof about 70,000 chest x-rays.
他的白细胞再造功能已经被完全破坏了
His abilityto create white blood cells,has been completely destroyed.
这就是他不能摆脱感染的原因
That's why he can'tfight off this infection?
他需要骨髓移植术
He's gonna needa bone marrow transplant.
我们要再做一次正电子放射断层扫描
And we did another mri.
他的脊柱里有很多血管瘤
There's a cavernous angiomawithin his spinal cord.
那是肿瘤
It's a tumor.
这就是引起休克和中枢神经系统症状的原因了
That's what's been causingthe shocks ,and cns symptoms.
他的脊柱里面有肿瘤?
He has a tumor insideof his spinal cord?
脊柱是一束束的纤维组成的,就像那种风筝线
The cord is made of strands put together,,sort of like a kite string.
手术要把这些一束束的纤维分开,然后切除肿瘤
The surgeon should be able to pull the strands ,apart and excise the tumor.
他这个手术的风险极高
Surgery on someone who's ashemopoetically,compromised as your sonis extremely risky.
如果他不做手术的话,我是说...
And,if you don't dothe surgery, I mean...
肿瘤将会停止他的呼吸
the tumor could causehis breathing to stop.
也许停止心跳
Possibly his heart as well.
你不知道要发生什么
There's no wayyou could have known.
你最好跟我们来
You're gonna haveto come with us.
你自己也要开始治疗
You need to start treatmentyourself.
不
No, no, no, no.
我过会儿
I can startmy treatment later.
但他不能
But he can'T.
他要送进隔离室防止进一步的感染
He needs to bein a sterile isolation room,to preventfurther infections.
- 妈妈,- 我们来早了
-Mom.,-We're early.
见到你真高兴
It's great to see you.
greg,不要骗人
greg,don't lie.
我们来的不是时候,对吗?
We came at a bad time.Didn't we?
实际上是的
Actually, yeah.
你们的好意我心领了,改日再聚吧
I have to take a rain check.
计划都订好了
plans have been made.
Wilson已经订好了
Wilson made 'em.
我叫他取消了的
I asked him to cancel.
我正在处理意见棘手的病例
I'm dealing with kindof a complicated case,right now.
好吧,等情况失控了我们再过来
Well,we'll just come back when things aren't,so out of control.
我们这组都很忙
My team is busy.
你不想见我们
You don't wanna see us.
妈妈,别让我感到罪过
Mom, don't make mefeel guilty.
不,不,当然不,对不起
No, no.Of course not, sorry.
我现在有个病人可能马上就因为放射感染而死了
I've got a patient who's probably gonna die,of radiation poisoning.
所以你就不能吃饭了
So that meansyou can't eat.
好吧,我们就在餐厅里随便吃点
Come on, let's grab a bitein the cafeteria.
我给你们买三明治
I'll buy youa reuben.
我想我还可以吃个三明治
I guess I got timefor a sandwich.
进来
Good.
我来告诉你carnell准备好手术了
I just wanted to let you knowcarnell's prepped,for surgery.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨,我是allison cameron.
Hi, I'm allison cameron.
我是你们儿子的同事
I work with your son.
greg 跟我们提起过你
Greg's told usall about you.
真的吗?
Really?
新来的
New?
不是,只是比较好骗
Nope, just gullible.
对不起,我只是开我儿子的玩笑
I'm sorry.I was just making fun of my son.
不是你
Not of you.
我们正要去吃点东西
We were just about to goto get something to eat.
愿意跟我们一起吗?
Would you careto join us?
你们很久没跟儿子在一起了
You don't havea lot of time with your son.
下次吧
Maybe another time.
你喜欢披头士吗?
do you like the beatles?
他们很好
They're all right.
我12岁的孩子正在问我这些问题
My 12-year-old just turned meback onto them.
Mccattney比上帝都有钱了
Mccartney's gotta havemore money than god.
这就是了
I think that's all of it.
翻个身
Reverse him.
他怎么样?
How's he doing?
看上去很好
Looks pretty good down here.
我棒极了，是不是?
Do I rock, or what?
他的血压在下降
his pressure's dropping.
再给他两单位
Give him another two units.
已经给了
I did already.
心率下降
His heart rate's falling.
他在不断出血.
He's hemorrhaging.
他们在说他妈妈上一次去牙医那
they're talking about mom's last trip,to the dentist.
成年人跟父母讲话
Grown children talking to their parents,
没什么好讲的
nothing gets talked about.
相信我.你什么都没错过
Trust me.You're not missing anything.
除了工作你还做什么?
So besides work,what you been up to?
没什么
Not much.
你总说
you always say that.
没什么
Not much.
这个永远都是答案
It's alwaysthe answer.
没有新意
Any new babes you might wanna tell me about?
饶了他吧,john
Leave him alone, john.
我买了辆新摩托车
I got a new motorcycle.
你可以在前面看到
You might have seen itout front.
桔黄色和一些大条纹
It's orangewith a gigantic scrape.
就是停在残疾人停车处的那个?
Is it the onein the handicapped parking?
看上去很糟,但是开起来很快
Looks like crap,but it drives great.
好,小心些好吗?
Well, you'll be careful, right?
上次我看见你时还有两条腿
Last I checked you still have two legs.
其实是三条
Actually three.
你知道你的问题出在哪儿吗?
You know whatyour problem is, greg?
换档变速?
Shifting gears?
你一直不知道你有多幸运
You just don't knowhow lucky you are.
上司在哪里?
where's the head?
他终于走了
Good thing we gotthat cleared up.
他只想帮你
He was justtrying to help.
我不需要帮助
I don't need help.
我知道
I know.
你就是这样一个人
You're absolutely perfect just the way,you are.
谢谢
Thank you.
他还要多久?
So how much longer do you think he'll be,in surgery?
很难说
It's hard to say.
ann死的时候他才开始上学
You know, he just started school when ann died.
我一团糟
I was a mess.
还在想怎么做个好家长
still adjustingto being a parent,
不只是个单亲家长
much less a single parent.
我常常只会放些冷蛋糕在他的饭盒里
You know, I used to put coldpancakes in,his lunch box.
这是我唯一会做的他可以吃的东西
I mean, that was the only thingI could make,that he would eat.
你做的很好.他是个好孩子
You did okay.He's a good kid.
他怎么样?
So how is he?
手术移走了肿瘤,没有伤害到脊髓
Well, the surgeonhas removed the tumor without,damagingthe spinal cord.
但是感染引起了另一些肠穿孔
But the infection has caused another,intestinal perforation.
我们止住血了,但是白细胞还是在下降
We stopped the bleeding, buthis white count,keeps falling.
好
Okay.All right.
那现在怎么办?
So what now?
用别的药?
Another drug?
抗生素?别的?
Antibiotics?What?
对不起
I'm sorry.
事实是无论我们给他什么
The reality is no matter what we give him,
他都挺不过来
it's unlikely he's gonna be able to fight,off the infections.
好
Okay.Okay.
他父亲和朋友都在治疗的很好
The father and the friend areresponding,well to treatment.
carnell的情况不太好
Things aren't looking so goodfor carnell.
谢谢....我们没有吃东西
Thank you...for not eating.
跟我没关系
It was none of my business.
他们看上去很高兴,不是吗?
They seem perfectly pleasant,don't they?
他们很高兴
They are.
他是海军飞行员
He was a marine pilot.
她是家庭主妇
She was a housewife.
结婚47年了
Married 47 years.
只有一个孩子
They had one child.
我妈妈跟普通人一样
My mom is justlike everyone else.
她很好
She's nice enough.
很有幽默感.讨厌吵架
Great sense of humor.Hates confrontation.
我爸跟你一样
My dad's just like you.
突然跳出来关心你
Not the caring-till-your-eyespop-out part.
只是一些荒谬的道德观念,叫你不要对任何人说任何谎话
Just the insane moral compass that won't let you,lie to anybody about anything.
这是做童子军和证人最好的品质
It's a great quality forboy scouts and,police witnesses.
却是一个好爸爸的最差品质
Crappy quality for a dad.
你觉得怎么样?
How you doing?
就这样
I'm hanging in there.
对不起,关于你妈我对你撒谎了
I'm sorry I liedto you about mom.
我也很抱歉对你撒谎了
I'm sorry I lied to you too.
她的死没有带来什么好处
There was nothing good that came out of her dying.
我没有生你的气
I'm not mad.
我知道你为什么这么做
I know whyyou did it.
它起作用了
It worked.
我从不喝酒也不开车
I never drink and drive.
爸爸,我害怕
I'm scared, dad.
没有关系
Come on.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothingto be scared of.
你要变好了
You're gonna be just fine.
别耍我
Don't play me.
我只想知道事实
I wanna know the truth.
我是在告诉你事实
I'm telling you the truth.
你会康复的
You're gonna be fine.
我发誓
I swear.
我爱你爸爸
I love you, dad.
我也爱你
I love you too.
为什么他不想见父母?
Why does he hate seeinghis parents?
因为他爸爸总是说实话,他不能接受这点?
So his dad tells the truth,he can't handle that?
他不想让他们失望
He hates being a disappointment.
他是个医生,世界著名的
He's a doctor.World famous.
他们怎么会失望?
How disappointedcan they be?
你知道的,这比看你儿子变成瘸子要好,比你看着你儿子变成捉摸不透的人要好
You knowwhat I figure is worse
House,-=结束=-
House.,Season 2 Episode 5